{"data":[{"question":"They had to be dismantle the vehicle to get them across the gorge.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"be","b":"vehicle","c":"to get","d":"across","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Be->x","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"I do wishes you would stop biting your nails, Brian! It really annoys me.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"wishes","b":"would","c":"biting","d":"annoys","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Wishes-> wish","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"Sarah wore dark glasses so to that no one would recognize her.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"wore","b":"to","c":"would","d":"her","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- To-> x","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"I found it when I was looking through some old paper.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"it","b":"when","c":"was looking","d":"paper","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Paper-> papers","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"I think you should tolerant of other people's weaknesses.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"think","b":"should tolerant","c":"other","d":"weaknesses","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Should tolerant-> should be tolerant","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"The cost of living has increasing so much that he finds it difficult to live within his income.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"living","b":"increasing","c":"much","d":"within","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Increasing-> increased","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"Uncle Ho's earnest desire was that our country might progress at equality rate with other countries in the world.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"earnest","b":"might","c":"equality","d":"with","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Equality-> equal","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"I am sure he shan't fail to keep his words.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"am","b":"shan't","c":"to keep","d":"words","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Shan't-> will","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"He very much surprised me when he said he was loving me.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"very much","b":"me","c":"said","d":"was loving","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Was loving-> had been loving","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"Throughout his speech, the boys were deeply attention.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Throughout","b":"speech","c":"deeply","d":"attention","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Attention-> attending","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"}]}